windows7themes.net 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy

_Worried about your privacy?_  
  
We care about your privacy and make very little use of cookies and do not collect any private information at all. You can control what type of advertising you see on our site by configuring your Google AdChoices. While you surf our website, you agree to our [Terms of Service](http://windows7themes.net/terms-of-usage)

windows7themes.net is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com, or endless.com, MYHABIT.com, SmallParts.com, or AmazonWireless.com. 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at 

support@windows7themes.net 

At www. **windows7themes.net** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.windows7themes.net and how it is used. 

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.windows7themes.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

www.windows7themes.net uses cookies to enhance downloads, but we do not collect any private information in any way and will never do. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include **Google Adsense, Doclix, Chitika, NeverBlue, IDG Tech and others.**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.windows7themes.net **** send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.windows7themes.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.windows7themes.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. 

Published: Sunday, March 8th, 2009  Last Modified: March 20, 2013

### Trending On Windows 7 Themes .Net

### Related Questions 

**Written by:**   
Oliver is the founder and lead editor of this site. He is interested in finding new ways to break Windows, find common errors and help others to fix them. Aside from that, he loves to fully customize systems with Rainmeter and Dreamscene, find out more about ancient civilizations like the Chachapoya, sharpen his digital photography skills and create software with a small group of selected developers. If you would like to connect with him to discuss anything, send him a mail!

Follow me on Twitter for daily updates:

Contact The Author:   

Connect With Our Site: 

_Need help? Ask a question at our QA site, click the red button to get started:_

 **Want to support us?** Great, simply buy your favorite games from G2A via our referral link (g2a.com/r/win7themes) and save money at the same time:
